greateats.com 2012-12-15

# 

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to every visitor ("Visitor") to this website at www.greateats.com ("Website"). Viewing and/or using and/or communicating with the Website constitutes acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy. The Website is not for any one under the age of 18 or otherwise covered by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act.

#### Collection of Information about Visitors

The Website routinely collects information about Visitors. Information is obtained in various ways, including the following examples: (1) pages or pop-ups where Visitors enter information, (2) orders for products or services from Visitors, (3) email inquiries, (4) telephone, mail or other communication with the Website, (5) Visitor interaction with banners, pop-ups or Website advertisers, (6) surveys, (7) registrations, (8) recognition of the IP Address of the device, such as the Visitor's computer, which is connected to the Website, and (9) cookies, which are discussed further immediately below.

#### Cookies

"Cookies" are bits of data placed by the Website onto a Visitor's computer. Sometimes, cookies come in the form of single-pixel gif images, also known as web bugs or web beacons. The Website may use cookies in various ways, including the following examples: (1) to keep a Visitor "logged on" to the Website, (2) to keep track of search criteria, (3) to monitor a Visitor's use, (4) to obtain information about a Visitor's computer, (5) to electronically gather information about a Visitor. A Visitor can choose whether or not to accept cookies by changing computer settings. If a Visitor chooses not to accept cookies, experience with the Website (and other websites) may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

#### Examples of Collected Information

Information collected by the Website includes the following examples: (1) information entered by Visitors, including name, address, telephone number and email address, (2) information about Visitors and Visitors' computers which is collected electronically by the Website, (3) the same information collected about Visitors may be collected from someone such as a friend to whom Visitors send emails from this Website, or to whom Visitors send the URL or a page of the Website, and (4) credit card information.

#### Using and Disclosing Collected Information

Collected information may be used for commercial solicitation and/or general marketing and/or other commercial purposes by the Website. Collected information may be combined and/or compared with other information collected from other websites and/or elsewhere. Collected information may be used to create other information about Visitors and about others, such as behavioral profiles and buying habits. Collected information may be disclosed to and shared with outside third parties for all of the same purposes. In addition, the Website will disclose information when required by law, or if the Website believes that such disclosure is warranted to:  
1) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Website;  
2) Protect and defend the rights or property of the Website, or Visitors to the Website;   
3) Identify persons who may be violating the law, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the Website;   
4) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

#### Interaction with Other Websites

If Visitors click on banners and/or pop-ups and/or hyperlinked advertising from the Website, they must assume that information is being collected about them, and the Website is not responsible for the use of information collected. Also, the Website is not responsible for the content of the landing pages and/or websites to which Visitors are linked.

#### Bulletin Boards and Public Forums

Visitors who use any site providing bulletin boards or other public forums, such as chat rooms, should be aware that the Website does not monitor these services. The Website does not protect Visitors in any manner regarding information Visitors post publicly and/or share with anyone else, including information about the Website's products and/or services.

#### Security and Transfers

The Website uses reasonable precautions to keep its information secure. The Website reserves the right to transfer all its information in connection with the sale of all or part of its business, capital stock or assets. The Website is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. The Website is not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

#### Opt-In Announcement and List Privacy Policy

GreatEats.com is an aggregator of opt-in email programs. Each program is subject to a separate privacy policy independent of this one. By submitting your information on this site you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of a 3rd party. Visitors should only submit their information to 3rd parties that they wish to receive emails from. Visitors may stop the arrival of these emails at any time by removing their e-mail addresses from the list by following the instructions on the e-mails they receive. Additionally, GreatEats.com will maintain its own customer database that visitors have the option to opt-in to when submitting their information in certain areas of the GreatEats.com site. GreatEats.com will not rent or sell your information to 3rd parties but may send messages on their behalf. 

#### Google Analytics

The GreatEats.com website employs Google Analytics to measure website statistics and enhance the visitor experience. GreatEats.com agrees to and abides by the Google Analytics terms of service which can be viewed [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/tos.html). 

#### Changes

This Privacy Policy may be changed at any time. Visitors should check the Privacy Policy each time they visit the Website. Use of the Website constitutes acceptance of the Privacy Policy and changes. The last update was made on November 2, 2011.
